ظآزI found a faint light
in the fading duskظآز
ظآزAnd met your steady gazeظآز
ظآزOne knowing glance,
and side by side we walk onظآز
ظآزLonging finds no place to restظآز
ظآزThrough drifting wind and rainظآز
ظآزYou are the prayer within my handsظآز
ظآزA single second frozen,
tears in focus, my heart already knowsظآز
ظآزWe made a promise long agoظآز
ظآزFor all our days to comeظآز
ظآزYou are the fate I cannot outrunظآز
ظآزHow much must I let go
to trade for one moment?ظآز
ظآزHolding you closeظآز
ظآزWould that be enough?ظآز
=Echoes of Love=
(Adapted from the signed screenplay
Echoes of Love on Migu Reading)
=Episode 16=
ظآزEven if I drift
within a darkened whirlظآز
ظآزKindred souls
meet the light and become oneظآز
Let me see.
I'm fine.
It stopped hurting long ago.
ظآزThe night runs deep like watching eyesظآز
You've suffered.
ظآزWave after wave of sorrowظآز
All of this
should come to an end.
ظآزLonging finds no place to restظآز
ظآزThrough drifting wind and rainظآز
ظآزYou are the prayer within my handsظآز
ظآزA single second frozen,
tears in focus, my heart already knowsظآز
ظآزWe made a promise long agoظآز
ظآزFor all our days to comeظآز
ظآزYou are the fate I cannot outrunظآز
ظآزHow much must I let go
to trade for one moment?ظآز
ظآزHolding you closeظآز
ظآزWould that be enough?ظآز
ظآزYou gave me a silent dreamظآز
ظآزTime rushed by,
yet the memories linger longظآز
ظآزCarrying the weight of hatredظآز
ظآزBurying every trace of loveظآز
ظآزI found a faint light
in the fading duskظآز
ظآزAnd met your steady gazeظآز
ظآزOne knowing glance,
and side by side we walk onظآز
ظآزLonging finds no place to restظآز
ظآزThrough drifting wind and rainظآز
ظآزYou are the prayer within my handsظآز
ظآزA single second frozen,
tears in focus, my heart already knowsظآز
ظآزWe made a promise long agoظآز
ظآزFor all our days to comeظآز
ظآزYou are the fate I cannot outrunظآز
ظآزHow much must I let go
to trade for one moment?ظآز
ظآزHolding you closeظآز
ظآزWould that be enough?ظآز
ظآزLonging finds no place to restظآز
ظآزThrough drifting wind and rainظآز
ظآزYou are the prayer within my handsظآز
ظآزA single second frozen, tears in focusظآز
As expected of Huanyue House's
finest courtesan queen.
A beauty that stirs the heart.
ظآزWe made a promise long agoظآز
ظآزFor all our days to comeظآز
ظآزYou are the fate I cannot outrunظآز
ظآزHow much must I let go
to trade for one moment?ظآز
But no matter how beautiful,
in their eyes,
I am nothing more than a plaything.
Beauty is not a sin.
The ones who deserve punishment
are them.
This day
is about to change.
The Shengtang Guild's
assassins arrived quickly.
Zhiyun.
Stay behind me.
Get back.
Let none of them escape. Kill them all.
Charge.
Shanguan Yu!
Go. Now.
Shanguan Yu.
Are you alright?
Ruyan.
I can only
walk this road with you so far.
You must walk
the rest of the road on your own.
No, Shanguan Yu.
Did you not want
to see those villains punished?
We are about to reach
the Court of Judicial Review.
You cannot leave me halfway.
Zhiyun.
I do not know why,
but I keep thinking
of our days in the thatched hut.
Though life was hard,
we were happy.
But at that time,
all I could think about was revenge.
I left you there alone.
ظآزStrangers meet again,
the past ablaze in vivid huesظآز
I am sorry.
ظآزA sharp arrow pierces through memoryظآز
ظآزLonging spreads like inkظآز
ظآزBeaded curtains divide love
and hate at either endظآز
Do not say such nonsense.
You will recover.
We still have to
avenge our wrongs together.
And live a good life together.
ظآزIn giving all, we found our only joyظآز
ظآزThat year we laughed
beneath pear blossomsظآز
ظآزOne night of snow
fell wild and restlessظآز
ظآزEvery perfect ending
hides a trace of regretظآز
ظآزWith blood upon my heart,
I bid love farewellظآز
ظآزNo more longing will enter my dreamsظآز
ظآزWhen all fades to drifting clouds,
may I share lasting peace with youظآز
ظآزAfter endless sorrow endured
love is a word too hard to severظآز
ظآزPast ties fade like a dream gone coldظآز
ظآزIn giving all, we found our only joyظآز
ظآزThat year we laughed
beneath pear blossomsظآز
ظآزOne night of snow
fell wild and restlessظآز
Shanguan Yu.
ظآزEvery perfect ending
hides a trace of regretظآز
ظآزWith blood upon my heart,
I bid love farewellظآز
ظآزNo more longing will enter my dreamsظآز
ظآزWhen all fades to drifting clouds,
may I share lasting peace with youظآز
Shanguan Yu.
(The Court of Judicial Review)
Hey, stop.
What are you doing?
Official,
I have an urgent case to report.
You?
You are only a lone woman,
not a lady of rank.
What grounds do you have
to sound the drum for justice?
Whatever it is, wait until dawn.
This is improper.
Official,
I wish to accuse
Grand Commandant Gao Deng
and Zhou Zihua of Huanyue House.
They colluded in secret,
trafficking courtesans,
and treating lives as worthless.
I beg you for mercy.
Please allow me
to beat the drum for justice.
Petty disputes among brothel women,
are worth you coming all this way?
Go on.
Do not defile this place.
I beg you, Official.
You woman,
why will you not listen?
(Is there truly)
(no place in this world that
will grant justice to women like us?)
(How many lives cry out in misery?)
Are you leaving or not?
(How many wronged souls cannot rest?)
If you do not leave now,
I truly will have you locked up.
- (I refuse to believe it.)
- Leave now!
(The Court of Judicial Review)
Oh no, what are we going to do?
This...
(The Court of Judicial Review)
Fire! Fire!